Aladdin Company Records Collection 1907-1989 (bulk 1940-1982)
Clarke Historical Library
- Aladdin Company Collection - Series #2, (Financial Records, 1910-1984)
  - Records, Sept. 1926-84 (lacking Oct. 1930) (4 folders),1926-1984 (Box 25, Folder 716)
  - Records, Sept. 1926-84 (lacking Oct. 1930) (4 folders),1926-1984 (Box 25, Folder 717)
  - Records, Sept. 1926-84 (lacking Oct. 1930) (4 folders),1926-1984 (Box 25, Folder 718)
  - Records, Sept. 1926-84 (lacking Oct. 1930) (4 folders),1926-1984 (Box 25, Folder 719)
  - Records, Cash sales, 1969; and sample cash book, April 1955 and January-March 1958,1955-1969 (Box 25, Folder 720)
  - Records, Appraisal, October 7, 1952 (2 folders),1952 (Box 26, Folder 721)
  - Records, Appraisal, October 7, 1952 (2 folders),1952 (Box 26, Folder 722)
  - Records, Appraisal, January 31, 1957 (2 folders),1957 (Box 26, Folder 723)
  - Records, Appraisal, January 31, 1957 (2 folders),1957 (Box 26, Folder 724)
  - Records, Letters re surplus equipment, equipment lists,1963 (Box 26, Folder 725)
  - Records, Appraisal, June 1, 1964,1964 (Box 26, Folder 726)
  - Records, Appraisal, June 6, 1970,1970 (Box 26, Folder 727)
  - Records, Letter re appraisal. September 5, 1979,1979 (Box 26, Folder 728)
  - Records, Inventory, September 1, 1942. Including draft of Hattiesburg, Mississippi,1942 (Box 26, Folder 729)
  - Records, Inventory, August 1,1943,1943 (Box 26, Folder 730)
  - Records, Original inventory, August 1943,1943 (Box 26, Folder 731)
  - Records, Inventory, October 1, 1950,1950 (Box 26, Folder 732)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 733)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 734)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 735)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 736)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 737)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 738)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 739)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 740)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 741)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 742)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 743)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 744)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 745)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 746)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 747)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 748)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 749)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 750)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 751)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 752)
  - Records, Annual Inventory (21 folders),1964-1984 (Box 26, Folder 753)
  - Records, Lumber purchased,1942 (Box 26, Folder 754)
  - Records, Lumber purchased,1943 (Box 26, Folder 755)
  - Records, Lumber Prices- Grades. Sample lists of materials for 200 houses, safe loads,1921 (Box 26, Folder 756)
  - Records, Base costs of materials for Mills,1941 (Box 26, Folder 757)
  - Records, Macon, GA Mill. Order filled,1941 (Box 26, Folder 758)
  - Records, Expediting Division, W.V. Sovereign’s Orders,1942 (Box 26, Folder 759)
  - Records, Wilmington, NC, Mill, construction, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 760)
  - Records, Hardware Checklist, sheets,1968 (Box 26, Folder 761)
  - Records, Standard Mitre Cuts, construction,undated (Box 26, Folder 762)
  - Records, Payroll journal. Partial,1953-1954 (Box 27, Folder 763)
  - Records, Payroll journal. Partial,1955-1956 (Box 27, Folder 764)
  - Records, Payroll journal. Partial,1959-1960, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 765)
  - Records, Payroll journal. Partial,1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 766)
  - Records, Payroll journal. Partial,1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 767)
  - Records, Payroll journal. Partial,1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 768)
  - Records, Payroll journal. Partial,1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 769)
  - Records, Payroll journal. Partial,1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 770)
  - Records, Payroll journal. Partial,1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 771)
  - Records, Payroll journal. Partial,1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 772)
  - Records, Box of loose payroll journal pages,1953-1956 (Box 28, Folder 773)
  - Records, Box of loose payroll journal pages,1959-1967 (Box 29, Folder 774)
  - Records, Box of loose payroll journal pages,1968-1978 (Box 30, Folder 775)
  - Records, Loose payroll cards- “Gross Payroll Balances- First Half, 1963-1976”/ Balance Sheet 1953-1962/ Payroll cards A-K 1953-1983,1953-1983 (Box 31, Folder 776)
  - Records, Loose payroll cards- K-Z,1951-1983 (Box 32, Folder 777)
  - Records, Alex Lincoln employee records,1948-1962 (Box 32, Folder 778)
  - Records, Rubis Folder – employee records,1953-1961 (Box 32, Folder 779)
  - Records, Loose payroll cards- “Vacation-Mill” (1948-1952)- “New” (5/22/51), incl. A-Z,1948-1952 (Box 33, Folder 780)
  - Records, Payroll cards,1937 (Box 34, Folder 781)
  - Records, Payroll cards,1937-1938 (Box 34, Folder 782)
  - Records, Payroll cards,1939 (Box 34, Folder 783)
  - Records, Payroll cards, 1940 “1941 in back",1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 784)
  - Records, Payroll cards A-B,1942 (Box 34, Folder 785)
  - Records, Payroll cards C-F,1942 (Box 34, Folder 786)
  - Records, Payroll cards G-I,1942 (Box 34, Folder 787)
  - Records, Payroll cards J-K,1942 (Box 34, Folder 788)
  - Records, HPayroll cards J-L,1942 (Box 34, Folder 789)
  - Records, Payroll cards M-O,1942 (Box 34, Folder 790)
  - Records, Payroll cards “S”,1942 (Box 34, Folder 791)
  - Records, Payroll cards P,R,T,1942 (Box 34, Folder 792)
  - Records, Payroll cards T-U,1942 (Box 34, Folder 793)
  - Records, Payroll cards W-Z,1942 (Box 34, Folder 794)
  - Records, Payroll cards A-L,1943 (Box 34, Folder 795)
  - Records, Payroll cards M-Z,1943 (Box 34, Folder 796)
  - Records, Payroll cards A-Z,1944 (Box 34, Folder 797)
- Aladdin Company Collection - Series #3, (Advertising, 1907-1985)
  - Records, Source Reports and Records,1907-1913 (Box 35, Folder 798)
  - Records, Source Reports and Records (2 folders),1911-1935 (Box 35, Folder 799)
  - Records, Source Reports and Records (2 folders),1911-1935 (Box 35, Folder 800)
  - Records, Source Reports and Records,1940-1941 (Box 35, Folder 801)
  - Records, Source Reports and Records,1949 (Box 35, Folder 803)
  - Records, Source Reports and Records,1950 (Box 35, Folder 802)
  - Records, Report book,1907-1912 (Box 35, Folder 804)
  - Records, Source Reports and Records,1940, 1953-1958 (Box 36, Folder 807)
  - Records, Source Reports and Records,1959 (Box 36, Folder 805)
  - Records, Source Reports and Records,1960 (Box 36, Folder 806)
  - Records, Source Reports and Records,1961 (Box 36, Folder 808)
  - Records, Advertising expenses, statistics,1912-1920 (Box 37, Folder 809)
  - Records, Source reports (2 folders),1913-1914 (Box 37, Folder 810)
  - Records, Source reports (2 folders),1913-1914 (Box 37, Folder 811)
  - Records, Advertising follow-up,1915-1922 (Box 37, Folder 812)
  - Records, Advertising Report,1929-1930 (Box 37, Folder 813)
  - Records, Advertising Report,1931-1932 (Box 37, Folder 814)
  - Records, Advertising Reports,1933-1935 (Box 37, Folder 815)
  - Records, Advertising Report, trailers, 1936 (Box 37, Folder 816)
  - Records, Source Reports (4 folders),1938-1950 (Box 37, Folder 817)
  - Records, Source Reports (4 folders),1938-1950 (Box 37, Folder 818)
  - Records, Source Reports (4 folders),1938-1950 (Box 37, Folder 819)
  - Records, Source Reports (4 folders),1938-1950 (Box 37, Folder 820)
  - Records, Advertising statistics, comparisons (H. V. White),1960 (Box 37, Folder 821)
  - Records, 1950 Source Records (1 of 2) and advertising schedule,1950 (Box 37, Folder 822)
  - Records, Advertising publications historical record (2 folders),1950 (Box 38, Folder 823)
  - Records, Advertising publications historical record (2 folders),1950 (Box 38, Folder 824)
  - Records, 1951 Source reports/ 1952-1956 Summaries,1951-1956 (Box 38, Folder 825)
  - Records, 1952 Source reports (partial)/ 1951-52 weekly competitive service reports,1951-1952 (Box 38, Folder 826)
  - Records, Advertising records,1952 (Box 38, Folder 827)
  - Records, Advertising records,1952 (Box 38, Folder 828)
  - Records, Advertising records1953 (Box 38, Folder 829)
  - Records, 1953 Source reports, analysis of advertising, 1954 advertising schedule,1953-1954 (Box 38, Folder 830)
  - Records, Source reports, advertising schedule,1954 (Box 38, Folder 831)
  - Records, Source reports, advertising schedule,1954 (Box 38, Folder 832)
  - Records, Source reports, sales receipts, ad schedule,1955 (Box 38, Folder 833)
  - Records, Advertising orders,1955-1956 (Box 39, Folder 834)
  - Records, Source reports,1956 (Box 39, Folder 835)
  - Records, Source reports,1957 (Box 39, Folder 836)
  - Records, Source reports,1957 (Box 39, Folder 837)
  - Records, Sales reports,1957 (Box 39, Folder 838)
  - Records, 1958 Advertising costs, 1959 advertising schedule,1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 839)
  - Records, Advertising schedule and report,1958 (Box 39, Folder 840)
  - Records, Advertising orders,1956-1960 (Box 39, Folder 841)
  - Records, Advertising orders,1956-1960 (Box 39, Folder 842)
  - Records, Source reports,1959-1960 (Box 39, Folder 843)
  - Records, Source reports,1961 (Box 39, Folder 844)
  - Records, Source reports,1962 (Box 39, Folder 845)
  - Records, Source reports and year-end summary,1963 (Box 39, Folder 846)
  - Records, Source reports,1963 (Box 39, Folder 847)
  - Records, Source reports,1964 (Box 39, Folder 848)
  - Records, Source reports,1969 (Box 39, Folder 849)
  - Records, Advertising schedule,1966 (Box 39, Folder 850)
  - Records, Source reports,1967 (Box 39, Folder 851)
  - Records, Source reports,1968 (Box 39, Folder 852)
  - Records, Source reports,1969 (Box 39, Folder 853)
  - Records, Source reports,1970 (Box 39, Folder 854)
  - Records, Source reports monthly Oct.-Dec. 1971, and sales reports. Monthly totals/ magazine year-end summary,1971 (Box 39, Folder 855)
  - Records, 1961-1970 Source reports (annual), 1953-1963 analysis of advertising,1953-1970 (Box 39, Folder 856)
  - Records, Source reports,1972-1982 (Box 40, Folder 857)
  - Records, Source reports,1972-1982 (Box 40, Folder 858)
  - Records, Source reports,1972-1982 (Box 40, Folder 859)
  - Records, Source reports,1972-1982 (Box 40, Folder 860)
  - Records, Source reports,1972-1982 (Box 40, Folder 861)
  - Records, Source reports,1972-1982 (Box 40, Folder 862)
  - Records, Source reports,1972-1982 (Box 40, Folder 863)
  - Records, Source reports,1972-1982 (Box 40, Folder 864)
  - Records, Source reports,1972-1982 (Box 40, Folder 865)
  - Records, Source reports,1972-1982 (Box 40, Folder 866)
  - Records, Source reports,1972-1982 (Box 40, Folder 867)
  - Records, Source reports,1972-1982 (Box 40, Folder 868)
  - Records, Newspaper and magazine ads,1910-1919 (Box 41, Folder 871)
  - Records, Newspaper and magazine ads,1920-1939 (Box 41, Folder 872)
  - Records, Newspaper and magazine ads,1940-1959 (Box 41, Folder 873)
  - Records, Newspaper and magazine ads,1960-1979 (Box 41, Folder 874)
  - Records, Competitor’s Advertising,1960-1970 (Box 41, Folder 870)
  - Records, Metropolitan Sunday Magazine Group (Scrapbook of 1949 Advertisements, _________, and Sales Records),1949 (Box 41, Folder 869)
  - Records, Catalog, brochures including summer cottages,advertisement,1908 (Box 42, Folder 875)
  - Records, Catalogs, spring (1) and fall (2),1909 (Box 42, Folder 876)
  - Records, Catalog, brochure, and advertisement,1910 (Box 42, Folder 877)
  - Records, Booklet, How Three Chicago School Teachers Built Their Aladdin Home-advertisement,1911 (Box 42, Folder 878)
  - Records, Catalog (1), Aladdin Interior (three including two different), brochures (2), and advertisements,1912 (Box 42, Folder 879)
  - Records, Catalogs (2) and brochures, advertisements,1913 (Box 42, Folder 880)
  - Records, Catalogs (2), The Aladdin Builders’ Safeguard (2), Advertisements, (2), Aladdin Interiors (2), Aladdin Homecraft Market Place (2), Farm Buildings (1), and brochures (2 folders),1914 (Box 42, Folder 881)
  - Records, Catalog 26 (4), Aladdin Bungalows, Summer Cottages,Fixtures, O.E. Sovereign copy of Aladdin Home-craft Market Place (2), and supplemental catalogs and brochures (2 folders),1915 (Box 42, Folder 882)
  - Records, Catalog 26 (4), Aladdin Bungalows, Summer Cottages,Fixtures, O.E. Sovereign copy of Aladdin Home-craft Market Place (2), and supplemental catalogs and brochures (2 folders),1915 (Box 42, Folder 883)
  - Records, Catalog 28 (2), and Manual of Construction, Aladdin’s Favorite Recipes, Merchandise catalogs of O. E. Sovereign & A. F. Huebner and paste-up copy of Aladdin Homecraft Market Place, Home equipment, Advance Messenger of Aladdin, furnace, and other brochures. (4 folders),1916 (Box 42, Folder 884)
  - Records, Catalog 28 (2), and Manual of Construction, Aladdin’s Favorite Recipes, Merchandise catalogs of O. E. Sovereign & A. F. Huebner and paste-up copy of Aladdin Homecraft Market Place, Home equipment, Advance Messenger of Aladdin, furnace, and other brochures. (4 folders),1916 (Box 42, Folder 885)
  - Records, Catalog 28 (2), and Manual of Construction, Aladdin’s Favorite Recipes, Merchandise catalogs of O. E. Sovereign & A. F. Huebner and paste-up copy of Aladdin Homecraft Market Place, Home equipment, Advance Messenger of Aladdin, furnace, and other brochures. (4 folders),1916 (Box 42, Folder 886)
  - Records, Catalog 28 (2), and Manual of Construction, Aladdin’s Favorite Recipes, Merchandise catalogs of O. E. Sovereign & A. F. Huebner and paste-up copy of Aladdin Homecraft Market Place, Home equipment, Advance Messenger of Aladdin, furnace, and other brochures. (4 folders),1916 (Box 42, Folder 887)
  - Records, Catalog 29 (O. E. Sovereign & N. Hamme copies), merchandise catalog of O. E. Sovereign, and paper copy of Furnishing for the Home, Readi-Cut Farm Buildings (Canadian), and A Little Journey to the Home of Aladdin (2 folders) ,1917 (Box 42, Folder 888)
  - Records, Catalog 29 (O. E. Sovereign & N. Hamme copies), merchandise catalog of O. E. Sovereign, and paper copy of Furnishing for the Home, Readi-Cut Farm Buildings (Canadian), and A Little Journey to the Home of Aladdin (2 folders),1917 (Box 42, Folder 889)
  - Records, Catalog 30 (2 copies including D.S. Betcone), Les Maisons Aladdin, (2 catalogs in French), and Aladdin Manual of Construction (2) Merchandise catalog (3 Copies including that of G.M. Price) (2 folders),1918 (Box 42, Folder 890)
  - Records, (891 is out as of 1-19-10): Catalog 30 (2 copies including D.S. Betcone), Les Maisons Aladdin, (2 catalogs in French), and Aladdin Manual of Construction (2) Merchandise catalog (3 Copies including that of G.M. Price) (2 folders),1918 (Box 42, Folder 891)
  - Records, Catalog 42 (2 copies),1929 (Box 42, Folder 892)
  - Records, Catalog 32 (4), New Colonial Bungalows and New Aladdinette Homes (2), and miscellaneous brochures (2 folders),1919 (Box 43, Folder 893)
  - Records, Catalog 32 (4), New Colonial Bungalows and New Aladdinette Homes (2), and miscellaneous brochures (2 folders),1919 (Box 43, Folder 894)
  - Records, New Colonial Bungalows and New Aladdinette Homes, Gun Club Houses, Industrial Housing bulletin catalog, and miscellaneous brochures (2 folders),1920 (Box 43, Folder 895)
  - Records, New Colonial Bungalows and New Aladdinette Homes, Gun Club Houses, Industrial Housing bulletin catalog, and miscellaneous brochures (2 folders),1920 (Box 43, Folder 896)
  - Records, Aladdinette Homes, Aladdin Homes Made in Canada (W.V. Sovereign copy), Instructions for the Erection Of your Aladdin Home (3), and miscellaneous brochures (2 folders),1921 (Box 43, Folder 897)
  - Records, Aladdinette Homes, Aladdin Homes Made in Canada (W.V. Sovereign copy), Instructions for the Erection Of your Aladdin Home (3), and miscellaneous brochures (2 folders),1921 (Box 43, Folder 898)
  - Records, Catalog 33 (2), Sale of discontinued designs, miscellaneous brochures,1922 (Box 43, Folder 899)
  - Records, Catalogs (4) (2 different; 2 copies of 1), A Solution for Japan’s Housing Problem (2) (2 folders),1923 (Box 43, Folder 900)
  - Records, Catalogs (4) (2 different; 2 copies of 1), A Solution for Japan’s Housing Problem (2) (2 folders),1923 (Box 43, Folder 901)
  - Records, Catalogs (2 different; 2 copies each), letter, miscellaneous brochures including summer cottages (3) (2 folders),1924 (Box 43, Folder 902)
  - Records, Catalogs (2 different; 2 copies each), letter, miscellaneous brochures including summer cottages (3) (2 folders),1924 (Box 43, Folder 903)
  - Records, Summer cottages brochure (2) and miscellaneous advertisements,1925 (Box 43, Folder 904)
  - Records, Catalog 37 (2), Spanish type catalog S-1 (2) (2 folders),1926 (Box 43, Folder 905)
  - Records, Catalog 37 (2), Spanish type catalog S-1 (2) (2 folders),1926 (Box 43, Folder 906)
  - Records, Catalog, (2 different types: 3 copies of 1, 3 marked up) Aladdin City, Florida, brochure, (3) manuscript copy of house brochures, Larger homes brochure (3), manuscript copies of houses, summer cottages, (3 including marked-up copy), house furnishings brochure (3), and other brochures (2 folders),1927 (Box 43, Folder 907)
  - Records, Catalog, (2 different types: 3 copies of 1, 3 marked up) Aladdin City, Florida, brochure, (3) manuscript copy of house brochures, Larger homes brochure (3), manuscript copies of houses, summer cottages, (3 including marked-up copy), house furnishings brochure (3), and other brochures (2 folders),1927 (Box 43, Folder 908)
  - Records, Catalog (2) Aladdin Homecraft Wall Coverings (Sample book), miscellaneous brochures, color card (2 folders),1928 (Box 43, Folder 909)
  - Records, Catalog (2) Aladdin Homecraft Wall Coverings (Sample book), miscellaneous brochures, color card (2 folders),1928 (Box 43, Folder 910)
  - Records, Catalog 42 (2) and miscellaneous brochures (2 folders),1929 (Box 43, Folder 911)
  - Records, Catalog 43 (5),1930 (Box 43, Folder 912)
  - Records, Catalog 44 (5) Used 1931, 1932, 1934,1931-1934 (Box 43, Folder 913)
  - Records, Catalog (4) (2 each of 2 different),1932 (Box 43, Folder 914)
  - Records, Catalog 45 (3) and follow-up,1933 (Box 43, Folder 915)
  - Records, Catalog (4), Trailer brochure,1934 (Box 44, Folder 916)
  - Records, Catalog 47 (3),1935 (Box 44, Folder 917)
  - Records, Catalog 48 (3) and follow-up, Everywhere is Home trailer brochure (6), Aladdin’s New Pullman Home (2 folders),1936 (Box 44, Folder 918)
  - Records, Catalog 48 (3) and follow-up, Everywhere is Home trailer brochure (6), Aladdin’s New Pullman Home (2 folders),1936 (Box 44, Folder 919)
  - Records, Catalog (2) and follow-up, Aladdin’s New Pullman Home brochures, mailing list (3 folders),1937 (Box 44, Folder 920)
  - Records, Catalog (2) and follow-up, Aladdin’s New Pullman Home brochures, mailing list (3 folders),1937 (Box 44, Folder 921)
  - Records, Catalog (2) and follow-up, Aladdin’s New Pullman Home brochures, mailing list (3 folders),1937 (Box 44, Folder 922)
  - Records, Catalog 49 (3 incl. 2 different) and follow-up,Homeward Bound and Low-Cost Homes catalogs,1938 (Box 44, Folder 923)
  - Records, Catalog 50 (4) and follow-up (2 folders),1939 (Box 44, Folder 924)
  - Records, Catalog 50 (4) and follow-up (2 folders),1939 (Box 44, Folder 925)
  - Records, Catalog 52 (2) and follow-up (2 folders),1940 (Box 44, Folder 926)
  - Records, Catalog 52 (2) and follow-up (2 folders),1940 (Box 44, Folder 927)
  - Records, Catalog (3), price lists, and follow-up (2 folders),1941 (Box 44, Folder 928)
  - Records, Catalog (3), price lists, and follow-up (2 folders),1941 (Box 44, Folder 929)
  - Records, Aladdin Five-Man Huts brochure (6), other military brochures, military project chart (2),1942 (Box 44, Folder 930)
  - Records, Prefab Brochure (W.E. Schultz copy),1943 (Box 44, Folder 931)
  - Records, Milling price list,1944 (Box 44, Folder 932)
  - Records, Catalog and price lists. (Note: This is a reprint of the 1941 catalog. See letter in 1946 folder),1945 (Box 44, Folder 933)
  - Records, Letter re government materials controls, catalog with paste-up French translation,1946 (Box 44, Folder 934)
  - Records, Miscellaneous direct mail advertisements,1940-1950 (Box 44, Folder 935)
  - Records, Catalog (4) (Note: This is a reprint of the 1941 catalog),1947 (Box 44, Folder 936)
  - Records, Catalog (4) and follow-up, catalogs with houses sold models changed (3) (2 folders),1948 (Box 44, Folder 937)
  - Records, Catalog (4) and follow-up, catalogs with houses sold models changed (3) (2 folders),1948 (Box 44, Folder 938)
  - Records, Catalog 54 (4) and follow-up, marked up catalogs, catalogs with notes (5), price lists, and miscellaneous material (2 folders),1949 (Box 44, Folder 939)
  - Records, Catalog 54 (4) and follow-up, marked up catalogs, catalogs with notes (5), price lists, and miscellaneous material (2 folders),1949 (Box 44, Folder 940)
  - Records, Catalog 55 (4), marked-up catalogs (4), lists of houses sold, model specs, The New Look in Homes for 1950 (2 copies including 1 with attached employee dinner invitation and list of long-term employees), Summer Cottages (6, incl. 1 with number of houses sold), photogravure brochure and letter,1950 (Box 44, Folder 941)
  - Records, Catalog 55 (4), marked-up catalogs (4), lists of houses sold, model specs, The New Look in Homes for 1950 (2 copies including 1 with attached employee dinner invitation and list of long-term employees), Summer Cottages (6, incl. 1 with number of houses sold), photogravure brochure and letter,1950 (Box 44, Folder 942)
  - Records, Catalogs (4), marked-up catalog (3) and follow up with Golden Rule letter brochures (8) (2 folders),1951 (Box 45, Folder 943)
  - Records, Catalogs (4), marked-up catalog (3) and follow up with Golden Rule letter brochures (8) (2 folders),1951 (Box 45, Folder 944)
  - Records, Catalog 57 (4), marked-up catalogs (2), follow-up, including Good Houses (5 copies), and other brochures (2 folders),1952 (Box 45, Folder 945)
  - Records, Catalog 57 (4), marked-up catalogs (2), follow-up, including Good Houses (5 copies), and other brochures (2 folders),1952 (Box 45, Folder 946)
  - Records, Marked up catalogs (6), follow-up and special spring follow-up, brochures: Golden Rule… (3), Readi-Cut Homes (4) paint brochure, list of sales (3 folders),1953 (Box 45, Folder 947)
  - Records, Marked up catalogs (6), follow-up and special spring follow-up, brochures: Golden Rule… (3), Readi-Cut Homes (4) paint brochure, list of sales (3 folders),1953 (Box 45, Folder 948)
  - Records, Marked up catalogs (6), follow-up and special spring follow-up, brochures: Golden Rule… (3), Readi-Cut Homes (4) paint brochure, list of sales (3 folders),1953 (Box 45, Folder 949)
  - Records, Catalog (3), follow-up, and extra follow-up including paint card (3 folders),1954 (Box 45, Folder 950)
  - Records, Catalog (3), follow-up, and extra follow-up including paint card (3 folders),1954 (Box 45, Folder 951)
  - Records, Catalog (3), follow-up, and extra follow-up including paint card (3 folders),1954 (Box 45, Folder 952)
  - Records, Catalog (5) including 3 marked-up, and brochures (2 folders),1955 (Box 45, Folder 953)
  - Records, Catalog (5), preview brochure (5), other brochures, follow-up, marked-up catalog, truss plan blueprint for 32’ x 74’ Westminister Church with list of Aladdin churches (3 folders),1956 (Box 46, Folder 954)